Hey guys, Bry Conturus here. This is
going to be a quick squat correction.
Um,
most people, the way they squat, you
will see them take a wide stance like
this, and then they'll squat like this.
And you look at their knees, they're
right here. They're not out here. I'd
rather see people take a narrower
stance, flare the feet out just a little
more, and then watch how far out I flare
my knees at the bottom. I come down and
I'm way out like that. I'm not here. I'm
not here. I'm way out right here. Big
difference. So again, this is the way
most people squat to here.
Take your stance in
way out to here and come up. Makes a big
difference. And a lot of people um have
knee pain and things like that when they
squat. This makes a big difference.